&gt；&gt；steve：好的，我们已经布置好了页面，
&gt;&gt; Steve: All right,
we've laid out the page,
希望我们不再打击DOM了。
hopefully we're not
thrashing the DOM anymore.
我们实际上需要到达最后的两个部分，这两个部分都是在涂抹图层，
We need to actually get to the final two
pieces, which is both painting the layers,
然后找出所有这些的轮廓，看看我们这里是否有一些问题。
and figuring out profiling of all of this,
and seeing if we have some problems here.
&gt；&gt；steve：所以任何时候你改变了不透明度或
&gt;&gt; Steve: So anytime you change
something other than opacity or
CSS变换，你会触发绘画，对吗？
a CSS transform,
you're gonna trigger a paint, right?
这很有趣，所以
And that's kind of interesting, so
似乎有东西可以改变而不需要重新画东西。
it seems like there are thing that can
change without having to redraw things.
就让那个洗刷你一秒钟。
Just let that one wash over you for
a second.
我将在一秒钟内解释它，但只需与之斗争片刻。
I will explain it in a second, but
just struggle with it for a moment.
尝试思考如何改变不透明度或
Of trying to think about how it is
that you can change the opacity or
移动东西而不必重新粉刷。
move stuff around without
having to repaint it.
感觉不对，是不是，仍然是真的，我没有骗你，但是
That doesn't feel right, does it,
it's still true, I'm not lying to you, but
这肯定有点违反直觉。
it's definitely somewhat counterintuitive.
好的，我们画一幅画，告诉浏览器，
All right, we do a paint,
we tell the browser,
浏览器告诉页面上的每个元素绘制自己的图片。
the browser tells every element on
the page to draw a picture of itself.
[笑]我觉得有点好笑，画一张你自己的画
[LAUGH] It's just kind of funny as I think
about it, draw a picture of yourself and
把它给我。
hand it to me.
[笑]然后它把这些放在一起，把页面放在一起。
[LAUGH] And then it takes those and
it puts together the page.
太棒了，它有所有这些信息，
Cool, it has all this information,
所有的东西都知道这个几何图形，因为我们已经完成了布局。
everything knows this geometry
cuz we've done the layout.
我们知道所有的风格是什么，它拥有做这件事所需的所有信息。
We know what all the styles are, it has
all the information it needs to do this.
我之前说过，触发布局总是会触发绘画，
And I said before, triggering
a layout will always trigger a paint,
因为现在有不同的像素要绘制。
because now there's
different pixels to paint.
酷，但是如果你只是在改变颜色，嘿，我只是在改变
Cool, but if you're just changing
colors like, hey, I'm just changing
背景颜色，你不一定需要触发布局。
the background color, you don't
necessarily need to trigger a layout.
所以你可以，每个布局都会导致油漆，但是
So you can have,
every layout is gonna cause a paint, but
并不是每幅画之前都有布局。
not every paint had a layout before it.
对，如果你在改变颜色，那就是重新粉刷。
Right, if you're changing colors,
that's just repainting.
如果你在改变尺寸，那就是布局和绘画。
If you're changing sizes,
that's layout and painting.
所以我们要做的就是弄清楚我们是不是在画不必要的画。
So what we wanna do is figure out
if we're painting unnecessarily.
再说一遍，这就是规则，你需要画多少画就画多少
Again, it's that rule,
paint as much as you need to and
只要你能逃脱惩罚。
as little as you can get away with it.
幸运的是，Chrome有一些非常棒的工具可以查看我们是否正在绘画，所以
Luckily, Chrome has some really great
tools to see if we're painting, so
我们去看看吧。
let's go take a look at that.
&gt；&gt；steve：在一个叫做卡住在顶部的例子中，
&gt;&gt; Steve: So
over in an example called Stuck On Top,
我有经典的粘贴页眉和页脚在底部，对吗？
I have the classic stuck header and
footer at the bottom, right?
我实际上可以继续，如果你不在控制台旁边渲染，
And I can actually go ahead, and if you
don't rendering next to the console,
这三个小点是你的花蕾。
these three little dots
here are your buds.
在那里你去更多的工具&gt；渲染，然后你应该把它放在这里。
Where you go to More Tools &gt; Rendering,
and then you should have it down here.
如果没有，无论是在聊天中还是在这里，如果有人对此有任何问题，
If not, either in the chat or here,
if anyone has a problem with that,
我们下次休息时再处理。
we'll handle it in the next break.
所以我们可以打开油漆闪光，然后
So we can turn on paint flashing, and
当页面被重新涂成绿色时，这会突出显示页面的各个区域。
this highlights areas of the page when
they're being repainted in green.
你可以看到，当我滚动时，我正在重新绘制标题和
And you can see as I scroll around
that I am repainting the header and
每次都是脚注。
footer every time.
如果你这样做而你看不到这一点，那是有原因的。
If you are doing that and
you don't see that, there is a reason.
我们会进入一点，但结果是如果你有一个视网膜屏幕，
We'll get into a little bit, but it turns
out that if you have a retina screen,
你现在不会这样。
that's not happening for you right now.
如果你有一个非视网膜屏幕，它是，对，
If you have a non-retina screen,
it is, right,
这就是为什么我在这个非视网膜设备模式。
that's why I'm in this
non-retina device mode.
我们将看看在视网膜和非视网膜上工作得同样糟糕的其他例子，
We'll look at other examples that work
just as poorly on retina and non-retina,
但这是一个非常简单的例子。
but this is kind of a very
simple example to look at.
我不知道，在我的工作中，除了
And I don't know, at my job,
everyone else except for
我有一个27英寸的迅雷显示器。
me has one of those 27-inch
thunderbolt displays.
所以在手机上，视网膜很好，我们在笔记本电脑前，但是
So on a phone, retina's good to go,
we're in front of our laptops, but
很多时候，当我们连接到监视器上时，它不是视网膜。
a lot of times when we're plugged
into a monitor, it's not retina.
至少在我的世界里，我有一个4k显示器，所以我不知道发生了什么。
At least in my world, I have a 4k display,
so I don't know what's going on.
酷，好吧，所以我们可以看到我们正在重新粉刷。
Cool, all right, so
we can see that we're repainting.
我们不想比我们需要的更多地重新粉刷。
We don't wanna repaint
more than we need to.
问题是，我们能做些什么呢？
And the question is,
what can we do about this?
&gt；&gt；steve：那么，再重复一遍，我们需要画多少就画多少，
&gt;&gt; Steve: So again, to kinda repeat
myself, we paint as much as we need to,
但只要我们能逃脱惩罚。
but as little as we can get away with.
我觉得我画的比我需要的要多，不需要展示那么多。
And I feel like I was painting more than
I needed to, to not show all that much.
所以在我们解决这个问题之前，
So before we can solve this problem,
我们在正在发生的事情中遗漏了一个概念性的部分。
we're missing a conceptual
piece in what's going on.
我说，嘿，我们把一切都安排好，我们计算款式，
I said, hey, we lay everything out,
we calculate the styles,
做所有这一切，告诉一切画自己，把它发送到GPU。
do all that, tell everything to
paint itself, send it to the GPU.
就像，任何时候有人说，是的，只要把它发送到GPU就行了
Like, anytime someone says something like,
yeah, just send it to the GPU and
他们真的会挥手，你应该用怀疑的态度对待他们。
they get really hand wavy,
you should treat them with suspicion.
在这一点上你应该怀疑我，因为我没有
And you should be treating me with
suspicion at this point because I didn't
解释一下这意味着什么，对吧。
explain what that even means, right.